orumarketplace.com 2019-04-06

# ORU Marketplace

This privacy policy relates to use of the **ORU MARKET** websites at [https://www.orumarketplace.com](https://www.orumarketplace.com/) and [http://www.orumarket.com](http://www.orumarket.com/)

This privacy policy covers how the **ORU Market** (hereafter named "we") will treat personal information that we collect. Personal information is your information and includes identifiers like your name, address, email address, and phone number.

Personal data is defined as any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person ('data subject'); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified, directly or indirectly, in particular by reference to an identifier such as a name, an identification number, location data, an online identifier or to one or more factors specific to the physical, physiological, genetic, mental, economic, cultural or social identity of that natural person.

ORU Market does NOT collect information related to special categories of personal data which include information about an individual's racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or similar beliefs, trade union membership (or non-membership), physical or mental health or condition, criminal offences, or related proceedings, and genetic and biometric information.

**Our Commitment To Privacy**  
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the **ORU Market** website. On several pages, you can buy products or services, make offers, counteroffers, negotiate, and make requests.  The types of personal information collected at these pages are:

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Demographic information  
IP Address information

**The Way We Use Information:**  
We use the information you provide about yourself when executing a transaction, only to complete that transaction. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that transaction, such as shipping and delivery companies.

We use the information you provide about someone else when creating a transaction only to ship the product and to confirm delivery. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that transaction.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website. 

We never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 12, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by logging into your **ORU Market** account and view your contact details. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information at any time by editing your market profile. 

We may update this policy at any time for any reason. If there are any significant changes to how we handle personal information, we will send a notice to the primary email address specified in your **ORU Market** account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

A data controller is a natural of legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal data; where the purposes and means of such processing are determined by law.

Processing is any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organization, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction.

This Privacy Policy and Data Protection Policy has been updated on: February 25, 2019

**Thank you and have an Orutopian day!**
